

# Hrushikesh Reddy

Computer Science Engineer

A high-energy student and prepared to contribute abilities to a given role while further developing acquired skills and gaining real-world experience. Highly organized, responsible, and a good motivator. Positively impact Team operations with top-notch communication and critical thinking skills.

- hrushikesh1204@gmail.com
- Vijayawada, India
- hrushikesh1204

#### 9491753660

- in linkedin.com/in/hrushikesh-reddy-79510616a
- github.com/HrushikeshReddy

## **EDUCATION**

# C.S.E (Specialization in Data Analytics) Vellore Institute of Technology

07/2017 - Present CGPA

- 8.43

# **Senior Secondary** Sri Chaitanya Junior College

06/2015 - 03/2017

CGPA

- 9.28

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Intern

Azure Skynet Solutions Pvt. Ltd.

04/2020 - 06/2020

Gurgoan, Haryana

Tasks

- E-Commerce Profitability and Recommendation System for Supermarket.
- Used Data Visualizations on dataset to find frequently sold items in the SuperMarket.
- Conducted Data Analysis on Products to assist in the increase in sales in Super-Market.

#### Intern

#### Shiash Info Solutions Pvt. Ltd.

01/2021 - 06/2021

Chennai.Tamilnadu

Tasks

- Connotation Seeking Strategy of Benefactor Info over Encrypted Data.
- Implemented Semantic Searching and Trapdoor Mechanism.

### CERTIFICATES

Data Science Professional Certificate (03/2020) 

Platform - COURSERA

Machine Learning with Python (05/2020) ☑

TABLEAU DESKTOP CERTIFIED PROFESSIONAL (08/2021) ♂

Platform - EDUTECHAZA

C++ - Course (06/2020) 🗷

Platform - SOLOLEARN

Platform - UDEMY

## **SKILLS**

Java, C++, Python SQL MSOffice MongoDB

HTML, CSS, JavaScript Prezi

## PERSONAL PROJECTS

Recommendation System for People in New places (03/2020 - 04/2020)

 Using the Idea of Mapping of Data developed a recommendation system for people in new places to assist in the choice of place to live or set up a new business.

Optical Character Recognition (Classic-CV Approach) (04/2020 - 05/2020)

 Applied filters to make the characters stand out from the background, used contour detection to recognize the characters one by one, and applied image classification to identify the characters.

Emotion Detection using Deep Learning (08/2020 - 01/2021)

- Developed a Facial Emotion Recognition model with the use of Convolutional Neural Networks.
- This resulted in an in-detail description of the emotion of a person in a particular time frame.

#### Payroll Management System (03/2018)

- It is a software program that enables the business to handle all the employee's records in a hassle free.
- Waterfall model is used in this project as SDLC.

### **SOFT SKILLS**

Team Player, Optimist, Adaptive, Problem-Solving

### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Qualified for Indian National Mathematical Olympiad(INMO) (01/2015)

760th Rank out of 136,000 Participants.

Player of the Tournament in Inter College Cricket Competition (12/2018 - 01/2019)

Captain of University Team in that Period. Helped the team to secure as RunnerUp in the Tournament.

Best Student of the year [2017-18] (07/2017 - 04/2018)

Recieved for an excellent performance in both Academics and Non-Academics

## **INTERESTS**

Volunteering Listening Music Cricket Tennis

Cooking Strategic Gaming Story Writing